Subtitles by DramaFever
Hello, I'm actor Hong Soo Hyun.
I've been living with my parents for 34 years.
Until several days ago, I am now living with new family members.
I'm half worried, half excited?
How would you feel if you had to live with strangers one day?
First meeting.
That moment of nervousness.
I'm meeting you for the first time without any makeup on.
The awkwardness was just for a moment
and it seemed like welcoming each other was a lot bigger.
With 11 different personalities and occupations
I'm sure it can't be easy living together under one roof, right?
Chan Yeol ate all of the pepper fried rice that Mama Shin
made even though he couldn't eat spicy foods.
I think I've moved up a level and matured.
Mama Shin even shaved off his mustache that he grew for 5 years by Bom's suggestion.
So Ra who is a very light sleeper couldn't say a word to the loud people at night.
Besides being worried, I had something in common with my roommate Nana.
And thanks to Dong Wook, Kang Joon was able to get a smart phone.
We're slowly starting to get to know one another by being considerate and understanding.
The first time the roommates are spending time together on a Sunday afternoon.
We've all decided to spend time with our own roommates today.
[So Ra, Bom, and Ga Yeon go shopping together!]
Which roommates do you think get along the best with one another?
[Sung Woo and Chan Yeol are making a flat bench!]
[Nana is teaching Soo Hyun how to dance the 'Catalina'!]
[Dong Wook and Se Ho is taking up a lip-sync challenge!]
[Min Woo and Kang Joon trying to find something in common!]
We are trying to mature and share our lives together by home sharing.
You're curious about what will happen today, right?
[Episode 3] [Love is an open door]
Come here.
It's late at night and there are two men who can't sleep.
Reporter Jo Se Ho.
- Yes, I'm Jo Se Ho. - I think it's time to get going.
Lee Dong Wook is going out to the scene.
This late at night.
Right now the time is...
- The time now. - The time now is 2:30 a.m.
It's 2:30 a.m. and Park Bom is still not home yet.
What is she doing right now? We are going to go and meet her personally.
Lee Dong Wonk will be going to the scene for an interview. He is going now.
- I'm going. - Move out.
You're going to start recording now?
It's kind of cold.
I'm going nuts. I think I'm going to have to accept royalty fees for this mist.